National Railroad Adjustment Board Case Files 5837
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- (Canadian Railwayman) (Extra Volume RYA Magazines) (Box 43)
  - Award No. 2663. Docket No. 2636. Lehigh Valley Railroad. RF Millard., 1970-1971 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Award No. 2665. Docket No. 2657. Chicago and North Western Railway Co. RR Robertson., 1971 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Award No. 2666. Docket No. 2658. Erie Lackawanna. EF Dunn., 1971 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Award No. 2667. Docket No. 2740. Texas and Pacific. Carl Stovall., 1970-1971 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Award No. 2668. Docket No. 2741. Terminal Railroad Association of St Louis. MA Hildebrand., 1970-1971 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Award No. 2669. Docket No. 2742. Terminal Railroad Association of St Louis. GL Rainwater., 1971 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Award No. 2670. Docket No. 2748. Penn Central. Philadelphia Territory, System Docket 352., Case 1-7-. RE Murray., 1971 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Award No. 2671. Docket No. 2638. Erie-Lackawanna Railroad Co. R Siwik., 1971 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Award No. 2672. Docket No. 2640. Baltimore and Ohio. C Kreg., 1969-1971 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Award No. 2674. Docket No. 2659. Erie Lackawanna. S Wasilewski., 1970-1972 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Award No. 2675. Docket No. 2662. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific Railroad., 1971 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Award No. 2682. Docket No. 2774. Erie Lackawanna. EF Dunn., 1971-1972 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Award No. 2683. Docket No. 2775. Erie Lackawanna. TJ Turcic., 1972 (Box 43, Folder 29)
- Public Law Board Files (RYA cases) Numbers 864 to 1995 (Box 44)
  - Award No. 2606. Docket No. 2579. Union Pacific Railroad. HN Wood, TR Pipes, GH May., 1970-1971 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Award No. 2607. Docket No. 2585. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific. HA Riedel., 1969-1971 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Award No. 2608. Docket No. 2586. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific. MM Vanko., 1969-1971 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Award No. 2609. Docket No. 2590. Port Terminal., 1971 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Award No. 2610. Docket No. 2593. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific. Various Yardmasters., 1970-1971 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Award No. 2611. Docket No. 2596. Southern Railway System. DE Lamberth., 1969-1971 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Award No. 2612. Docket No. 2608. Norfolk and Western Railway Co. FC Butler., 1969-1971 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Award No. 2615. Docket No. 2632. Seaboard Coast Line. Various Yardmasters., 1970 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Award No. 2616. Docket No. 2633. Seaboard Coast Line. Various Yardmasters., 1968-1971 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Award No. 2617. Docket No. 2634. Seaboard Coast Line. WD Harris., 1970-1971 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Award No. 2618. Docket No. 2635. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Co. JL Collins., 1971 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Award No. 2619. Docket No. 2620. Soo Line Railroad Co. ME Milz., 1971 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Award No. 2621. Docket No. 2625. Chicago and North Western Railway. WV Arter., 1970-1971 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Award No. 2622. Docket No. 2594. Patapsco and Back Rivers Railroad Co., 1966-1970 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Award No. 2623. Docket No. 2578. Lehigh Valley. CG Martin., 1969-1971 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Award No. 2626. Docket No. 2595. Penn Central Co. System Docket 310. Buffalo Division NN137. RJ Gaston., 1968-1971 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Award No. 2627. Docket No. 2599. Penn Central Co. System Docket No 313. Buffalo Division BD-35. AF Dachille., 1970-1971 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Award No. 2628. Docket No. 2601. Penn Central Co. System Docket 311. Buffalo Division Case NN-136. RW Inglut., 1968-1971 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Award No. 2629. Docket No. 2607. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific. Yardmaster Position 25 at Burnham Bridge., 1969-1971 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Award No. 2630. Docket No. 2611. Penn Central. DE Highfill., 1969-1971 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Award No. 2632. Docket No. 2613. Penn Central. RW Sitzler., 1971 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Award No. 2634. Docket No. 2627. Chicago River and Indiana. MR Jackson., 1971 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Award No. 2633. Docket No. 2614. Penn Central. Ross and Kravshaar., 1973 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Award No. 2637. Docket No. 2603. Penn Central Co. System Docket No. 304. Cincinnati Division, Case Y-13-68., 1970-1971 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Award No. 2638. Docket No. 2609. Norfolk and Western. Various Yardmasters. Frankfort, Indiana., 1970-1971 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Award No. 2640. Docket No. 2618. Fort Worth Belt Railway. RR Garrison., 1972-1973 (Box 44, Folder 26)
- Public Law Board Files (RYA cases) Numbers 2046 to 2719 (Box 45)
  - Award No. 3128. Docket No. 3093. Penn Central Transportation Co. PT Hart., 1974 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Award No. 3130. Docket No. 3030. Grand Trunk Western Railroad Co. RL Barker., 1972-1974 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Award No. 3135. Docket No. 3085. Boston and Maine Corporation. WW Avery., 1966-1974 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Award No. 3136. Docket No. 3086. Erie Lackawanna Railway Co. Kevin Gore., 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Award No. 3140. Docket No. 3122. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. DE Harmon., 1975 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Award No. 3144. Docket No. 3129. Santa Fe Railway Co. JA Wilson., 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Award No. 3146. Docket No. 3171. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific. DJ Berhow., 1974 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Award No. 3147. Docket No. 3172. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific. RR Worth., 1974 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Award No. 3148. Docket No. 3026. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Co. Various Yardmasters., 1973 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Award No. 3149. Docket No. 3047. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. VA Casanova., 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Award No. 3151. Docket No. 3176. Union Belt of Detroit. HR McClure., 1974 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Award No. 3155. Docket No. 3182. Boston and Maine. MR Cunio et al., 1974 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Award No. 3156. Docket No. 3109. Penn Central Transportation Co. VE Staley. System Docket 446., 1975 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Award No. 3158. Docket No. 3113. Penn Central Transportation Co. D Durham., 1973-1975 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Award No. 3159. Docket No. 3115. Erie Lackawanna. BE Conway., 1975 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Award No. 3160. Docket No. 3119. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Co. JG Safley., 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Award No. 3161. Docket No. 3116. Penn Central Transportation Co. System Docket 440., 1972-1975 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Award No. 3164. Docket No. 3204. Union Belt of Detroit. HR McClure., 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Award No. 3165. Docket No. 3205. Union Belt of Detroit. CA Guerriero., 1974 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Award No. 3166. Docket No. 3135. Lehigh Valley Railroad Co. Thomas McGovern., 1973-1975 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Award No. 3168. Docket No. 3137. Penn Central. CR Martin., 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Award No. 3169. Docket No. 3148. Penn Central. RW Smart., 1972-1974 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Award No. 3170. Docket No. 3130. Norfolk and Western. EE Stover., 1974 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Award No. 3171. Docket No. 3168. Union Pacific Railroad. ME Jung., 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Award No. 3173. Docket No 3169. Missouri Pacific Railroad. AV Dixon., 1973-1975 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Award No. 3175. Docket No. 3216. Burlington, Northern Inc. RR Pankratz., 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Award No. 3176. Docket No. 3117. Central of New Jersey. H Maybin, CJ Kelton., 1973-1975 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Award No. 3177. Docket No. 3120. Long Island Railroad. TC Cappetta, JN Zarra., 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Award No. 3179. Docket No. 3234. Penn Central. RT Ciulis. System Docket No. 495. Northeastern Region, Buffalo Division Case 21-73-123., 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Award No. 3180. Docket No. 3235. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Co. AJ Tuchek., 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Award No. 3181. Docket No. 3239. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Co. JA Byrne., 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder 31)
- National Mediation Board, Representations Elections for RYA Representation on Railroads Ann Arbor through NKP (Box 46)
  - Award No. 3080. Docket No. 3055. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific Railroad Co. RJ Sellner., 1972-1974 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Award No. 3081. Docket No. 3059. Boston and Maine Corporation. Martel, Willey, Davis., 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Award No. 3084. Docket No. 3075. Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac Railroad Co. LC Gorham., 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Award No. 3085. Docket No. 3102. Boston and Maine Corporation. JA LeVasseur., 1970-1974 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Award No. 3086. Docket No. 3131. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. WH Wysong., 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Award No. 3087. Docket No. 3132. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. TH Ernst., 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Award No. 3089. Docket No. 3097. Ralph Herman., 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Award No. 3090. Docket No. 3098. Boston and Maine Corporation. GM Kalil., 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Award No. 3091. Docket No. 3099. Penn Central Transportation Co. Docket 447. Southern Region, Columbus Division. Y-125-7., 1974 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Award No. 3092. Docket No. 3100. Penn Central Transportation Co. System Docket 445. Central Region, Valley Division Case 1-73., 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Award No. 3097. Docket No. 3107. Grand Trunk Western Railroad Co. RL Barker., 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Award No. 3098. Docket No. 3108. Grand Trunk Western Railroad Co. MH Goebel., 1974 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Award No. 3099. Docket No. 3046. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific Railroad Co. CJ Chase., 1974 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Award No. 3100. Docket No. 3054. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific Railroad Co. JR Becks., 1973 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Award No. 3102. Docket No. 3057. Lehigh Valley Railroad Co. H Messner., 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Award No. 3104. Docket No. 3084. Penn Central Transportation Co. ED Smith. Docket 443. Central Region, Pittsburgh Division., 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Award No. 3105. Docket No. 3092. Southern Railroad System. JL Joly. New Orleans, Louisiana., 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Award No. 3106. Docket No. 3126. Southern Railway System. JL Joly., 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Award No. 3107. Docket No. 3134. Norfolk and Western Railway Co. CE O'Hearn., 1974 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Award No. 3115. Docket No. 3145. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe., 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Award No. 3108. Docket No. 3138. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe., 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Award No. 3109. Docket No. 3139. Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe., 1973 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Award No. 3110. Docket No. 3140. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe., 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Award No. 3111. Docket No. 3141. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. SL Auckalls., 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Award No. 3112. Docket No. 3142. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. SL Nuckolls., 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Award No. 3113. Docket No. 3143. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. SL Nuckolls., 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Award No. 3114. Docket No. 3144. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. JB Lamascus., 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Award No. 3116. Docket No. 3146. P Ginepra., 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Award No. 3117. Docket No. 3147. Penn Central Transportation Co. CR Martin., 1972-1974 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Award No. 3118. Docket No. 3091. Central of Georgia Railroad Co. JR Plemmons., 1974 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Award No. 3120. Docket No. 3024. Penn Central, PJ Malizia., 1973-1975 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Award No. 3125. Docket No. 3087. Grand Trunk Western Railroad Co. George R Burk., 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Award No. 3126. Docket No. 3071. Penn Central. System Docket 436. Harrisburg Case W 34/71., 1971-1974 (Box 46, Folder 33)
- National Mediation Board, Representations Elections for RYA Representation on Railroads NYC through Y and S (Box 47)
  - Award No. 3211. Docket No. 3236. Grand Trunk Western. Burns, Scutt, Wallace and Shaw., 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Award No. 3212. Docket No. 3238. Fairport, Painesville and Eastern Railway Co. RG White., 1975 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Award No. 3213. Docket No. 3240. Penn Central. SJ Borowski., 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Award No. 3214. Docket No. 3153. Norfolk and Western Railway Co. EE Stover., 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Award No. 3217. Docket No. 3156. Penn Central. R Davis., 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Award No. 3218. Docket No. 3157. Penn Central Transportation Co. VE Stiller., 1974 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Award No. 3219. Docket No. 3158. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. W Wysong., 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Award No. 3220. Docket No. 3159. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. SL Nuckolls., 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Award No. 3221. Docket No. 3164. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. FL Mavity, Ginepra, Ernst., 1974 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Award No. 3222. Docket No. 3175. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. JD Annis., 1973-1975 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Award No. 3225. Docket No. 3226. St Louis-San Francisco Railway Co. GM Hooten., 1973-1975 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Award No. 3226. Docket No. 3227. Penn Central. FP Wike. System Docket 472. Eastern Region, Harrisburg Division., 1975 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Award No. 3228. Docket No. 3230. Penn Central. D Crooks., 1975 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Award No. 3229. Docket No. 3231. Grand Trunk Western Railroad Co. JD Weirs., 1975 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Award No. 3230. Docket No. 3233. Norfolk and Western. BG Whittaker., 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Award No. 3231. Docket No. 3237. Penn Central Transportation Co. RN Yontz., 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Award No. 3232. Docket No. 3241. Boston and Maine Corporation. EJ Bazin And ER Cote., 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Award No. 3234. Docket No. 3163. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. CM Hoagland., 1973-1975 (Box 47, Folder 18)
- Award No. 3182. Docket No. 3166. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. Evetts, Nuckolls, Mavity, Meehan., 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Award No. 3183. Docket No. 3160. St Louis-San Francisco Railway Co. JT Cole., 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Award No. 3184. Docket No. 3162. St Louis-San Francisco Railway Co. WS Smith., 1973-1975 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Award No. 3185. Docket No. 3197. Penn Central. Various Yardmasters., 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Award No. 3186. Docket No. 3198. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. JR Hays., 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Award No. 3187. Docket No. 3199. Penn Central. FW Carley., 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Award No. 3189. Docket No. 3243. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. W Haney., 1975 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Award No. 3191. Docket No. 3256. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. EL Richardson., 1975 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Award No. 3192. Docket No. 3167. St Louis-San Francisco Railway Co. M Rathje., 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Award No. 3193. Docket No. 3192. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. JJ Stec., 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Award No. 3194. Docket No. 3193. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. RL Landford, Corwith, Illinois., 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 11)
- Award No. 3195. Docket No. 3194. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. JH Rawlings., 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 12)
- Award No. 3196. Docket No. 3195. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. DL Timmons., 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Award No. 3197. Docket No. 3196. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. L Timmons., 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 14)
- Award No. 3198. Docket No. 3203. Penn Central. GE Lohr. System Docket 450. Central Region, Allegheny Division., 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 15)
- Award No. 3201. Docket No. 3149. St Louis-San Francisco Railway Co. PW Hackler., 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 16)
- Award No. 3202. Docket No. 3150. St Louis - San Francisco Railway Co. JL Brodrecht., 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 17)
- Award No. 3204. Docket No. 3152. Boston and Maine Corporation. CH Whitney and JW Morrissey., 1974-1976 (Box 48, Folder 18)
- Award No. 3205. Docket No. 3161. St Louis - San Francisco Railway Co. WM Sennett., 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 19)
- Award No. 3206. Docket No. 3220. Boston and Maine Corporation. VL McDonald and JS Hesson., 1975 (Box 48, Folder 20)
- Award No. 3208. Docket No. 3264. Erie Lackawanna Railway Co. Yardmasters 363 and 364., 1975 (Box 48, Folder 21)
- Award No. 3210. Docket No. 3232. Detroit Terminal. JJ Kozak., 1975 (Box 48, Folder 22)
- Award No. 2769. Docket No. 2648. Penn Central. System Docket 333. Chesapeake Division, Case 188-3280., 1969-1972 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Award No. 2773. Docket No. 2840. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific Railroad. Cedar Rapids., 1972 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Award No. 2774. Docket No. 2843. Penn Central. System Docket 379. AW Graham., 1972 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Award No. 2775. Docket No. 2860. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific Railroad. CR McClaren., 1972 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Award No. 2776. Docket No. 2861. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific Railroad. RJ Boon., 1972 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Award No. 2777. Docket No. 2863. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific Railroad. HJ Honeck., 1972 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Award No. 2778. Docket No. 2865. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific. Mertens., 1972 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Award No. 2779. Docket No. 2652. Penn Central. System Docket 327, Chesapeake Division., 1971-1972 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Award No. 2780. Docket No. 2678. Penn Central. System Docket 345. St Louis Division, Case YM-1-69., 1971-1972 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Award No. 2781. Docket No. 2684. Lehigh Valley. Alfred Feuerstein., 1971-1972 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Award No. 2783. Docket No. 2727. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific. WG Stotz., 1971-1972 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Award No. 2784. Docket No. 2747. Penn Central System Docket 353., 1971-1972 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Award No. 2789. Docket No. 2799. Penn Central. Pittsburgh Territory, System Docket No. 354. YM-16-70. W Filer., 1971-1972 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Award No. 2792. Docket No. 2810. Norfolk Southern Railway Co. WR Gibson., 1972 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Award No. 2793. Docket No. 2811. Erie Lackawanna. DE Clancy. Meadville, PA., 1972 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Award No. 2794. Docket No. 2814. Southern System. JW Hunter., 1972 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Award No. 2795. Docket No. 2666. Southern Railway. MB Holcome., 1971-1972 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Award No. 2798. Docket No. 2756. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. TF Brooks., 1971-1972 (Box 49, Folder 18)
- Award No. 2799. Docket No. 2776. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway., 1971-1972 (Box 49, Folder 19)
- Award No. 2800. Docket No. 2777. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. LG Lunn., 1971-1972 (Box 49, Folder 20)
- Award No. 2801. Docket No. 2780. Southern Railway. MF Armstrong., 1971-1972 (Box 49, Folder 21)
- Award No. 2803. Docket No. 2800. Union Pacific Railroad. T Hildebrand, VD Wood, CN Bessey., 1972 (Box 49, Folder 22)
- Award No. 2684. Docket No. 2641. Baltimore and Ohio. IH Throckmorton., 1971 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Award No. 2685. Docket No. 2643. Baltimore and Ohio. WG Ulrey., 1971 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Award No. 2686. Docket No. 2653. Erie Lackawanna. DE Clancy., 1971 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Award No. 2687. Docket No. 2720. Erie Lackawanna. DE Clancy., 1971 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Award No. 2688. Docket No. 2793. Erie Lackawanna. JP O'Donnell., 1971-1972 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Award No. 2689. Docket No. 2794. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. JC Conn., 1972 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Award No. 2690. Docket No. 2795. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. E Asher., 1972 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Award No. 2691. Docket No. 2796. Baltimore and Ohio Yardmaster. WG Innis., 1972 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Award No. 2692. Docket No. 2797. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. WA Stanley., 1972 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Award No. 2693. Docket No. 2798. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific. JA Crisci and WL Gilman., 1972 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Award No. 2694. Docket No. 2642. Baltimore and Ohio. EL Humble., 1971 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Award No. 2695. Docket No. 2655. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. VA Casanova., 1971-1972 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Award No. 2696. Docket No. 2709. Louisville and Nashville Railroad. SB West., 1971-1972 (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Award No. 2697. Docket No. 2718. Erie Lackawanna. FJ Crossfield., 1971-1972 (Box 50, Folder 14)
- Award No. 2698. Docket No. 2719. Erie Lackawanna. ME Kalopos., 1971-1972 (Box 50, Folder 15)
- Award No. 2704. Docket No. 2664. Kentucky and Indiana Terminal. TL Barnett., 1971-1972 (Box 50, Folder 16)
- Award No. 2706. Docket No. 2731. Norfolk and Western Railway. JJ Galvin., 1970-1972 (Box 50, Folder 17)
- Award No. 2707. Docket No. 2706. Chicago, Milwaukee and St Paul Railroad. DG Flowers., 1970-1972 (Box 50, Folder 18)
- Award No. 2710. Docket No. 2752. Union Belt of Detroit. C Gow., 1971-1972 (Box 50, Folder 19)
- Award No. 2711. Docket No. 2753. Union Belt of Detroit. C Gow., 1971-1972 (Box 50, Folder 20)
- Award No. 2712. Docket No. 2754. Chicago and North Western Railway. William E Melton., 1970-1972 (Box 50, Folder 21)
- Award No. 2713. Docket No. 2755. Chicago and North Western. William E Melton., 1971-1972 (Box 50, Folder 22)
- Award No. 2719. Docket No. 2725. Burlington Northern. BM Kult., 1971 (Box 50, Folder 23)
- Award No. 2720. Docket No. 2732. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. Unassigned Yardmasters., 1971-1972 (Box 50, Folder 24)
- Award No. 2723. Docket No. 2782. Minnesota Transfer Railway Co. Paul C Axelson., 1971-1972 (Box 50, Folder 25)
- Award No. 2724. Docket No. 2803. Texas and Pacific. JH Jackson., 1971-1972 (Box 50, Folder 26)
- Award No. 2725. Docket No. 2808. Southern Railway Co. JL Robinson., 1972 (Box 50, Folder 27)
- Award No. 2726. Docket No. 2809. Southern Railway System. JL Robinson., 1972 (Box 50, Folder 28)
- Award No. 2727. Docket No. 2817. Southern Railway System. JL Robinson., 1971-1972 (Box 50, Folder 29)
- Award No. 2765. Docket No. 2818. Penn Central. Mr. Moskal., 1972 (Box 50, Folder 30)
- Award No. 2766. Docket No. 2820. Southern Railway Co. HW Ritch., 1972 (Box 50, Folder 31)
- Award No. 2915. Docket No. 2904. Central of New Jersey. Thomas L Pearsall., 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Award No. 2917. Docket No. 2906. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Co. MV Gogerty., 1971-1973 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Award No. 2918. Docket No. 2907. Indiana Harbor Belt. Various Yardmasters., 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Award No. 2919. Docket No. 2908. Indiana Harbor Belt. GE Sawyer., 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Award No. 2920. Docket No. 2909. Indiana Harbor Belt. GE Sawyer., 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Award No. 2921. Docket No. 2910. Indiana Harbor Belt. FJ Bennett., 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Award No. 2922. Docket No. 2921. Grand Trunk Western Railroad. JP Fisher., 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Award No. 2923. Docket No. 2925. Grand Trunk Western Railroad Co. JP Fisher., 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Award No. 2924. Docket No. 2982. Penn Central. JA Patterson. System Docket 413. Pittsburgh Case 1-72-e., 1973 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Award No. 2925. Docket No. 2983. Norfolk and Western. FA Chambers, Jr., 1973 (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Award No. 2926. Docket No. 2984. Norfolk and Western. Lewis McCord, Jr., 1973 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- Award No. 2927. Docket No. 2985. Louisville and Nashville Railroad Co. Coakley, Duvall, Noble, Jones, Snapp., 1973 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Award No. 2928. Docket No. 2879. Texas and Pacific Railway. Yardmasters at Crest Tower., 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- Award No. 2929. Docket No. 2911. Indiana Harbor Belt. JO Lindsay., 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- Award No. 2930. Docket No. 2922. St Louis - San Francisco. TA Hallum. JO Whitten., 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 15)
- Award No. 2931. Docket No. 2926. Penn Central. John P Gately., 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 16)
- Award No. 2934. Docket No. 2934. Penn Central. CM Orlando., 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 17)
- Award No. 2937. Docket No. 2944. Penn Central. JH Dickson., 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 18)